前情提要：《犯罪心理》。进化》...
Previously on "Criminal Minds: Evolution"...
Lewis探员发现了一个乱葬岗
Agent Lewis uncovered a mass grave.
她将会留在华盛顿州
She'll be staying in Washington State.
我需要一些帮助
I'm gonna need some help.
Tara Lewis
Tara Lewis.
看上去这里有
Looks like there's been
几十年来一直有一个活跃的杀手在这里
an active killer up here for decades.
我们在一个被掩埋的海运集装箱里发现了16具尸体
We got 16 dead bodies in a buried shipping container.
David Rossi最后一次出现在办公室是什么时候?
When's the last time David Rossi was in the office?
人们都说是过去一年。
People are saying this past year,
Rossi探员一直很着迷
Agent Rossi's been obsessed.
这些年在地下室工作的经历让他着了魔。
All those years working in the basement caught up with him.
你在忙什么?
What're you working on?
亚历山大市的Westbrook家族
Westbrook family in Alexandria.
这不是入侵的问题
This isn't about invasion.
而是对一个家庭的破坏
It's about destruction of a family.
Chrissy Delaney是 "SOAR "的目标。
Chrissy Delaney was targeted on "SOAR."
这不可能 Luke，"SOAR "是无法破解的。
That's impossible. Luke, "SOAR" is unhackable.
我知道。我知道，是我在保护它。
I know. I'm the one that secured it.
对于一个19岁的孩子来说，这很复杂。
It's sophisticated for a 19-year-old kid.
我们在两岸有相同的储物柜的可能性有多大？
What are the chances we have identical foot lockers
我们在两岸有相同的储物柜吗？
on opposite coasts?
我们需要所有的人都关注这个。
We need all eyes on this.
什么...
What...
什么是...
What is...
我感觉不是很好。
I don't feel so good.
一，二，三。
One, two, three.
什么是... 发生了什么事？
What's... What's going on?
什么...
What...
你是什么...
What are you...
你能感觉到吗？
Can you feel that?
不，很好。
No. Good.
不，伙计，我... 我什么都感觉不到。
No, man, I c... I can't feel anything.
什么...
Wh...
等待，等待，等待，不！请... 请停下来！
Wait, wait, wait, no! P-P-Please stop!
请停下来！你在对我做什么？嘘！嘘！ 嘘！
Stop! What are you doing to me? Shh! Shh!
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
嘘！我希望你能仔细听好。
Shh! I want you to listen very carefully.
因为你们要做一个选择。
Because you have a choice to make.
训练师：还有20秒，队员们。
Workout trainer: 20 more seconds, team.
让我们向400分的士兵妈妈问好!
Let's say hello to Soldier Mom with 400 points!
900分的Ab-tastic。呜!
Ab-tastic with 900. Whoo!
还有哇，QueenBabyGirlYasssss得了高达8000分。
And wow, a whopping 8,000 to QueenBabyGirlYasssss.
你漏掉了一个S。
You left out an S.
继续吧。
Keep going.
? 哦！ ?
♪ Oh! ♪
# 哦！ # # Oh!
? 哦！ ?
♪ Oh! ♪
哦！
早上好，我可爱的动物们。
Good morning, my fabulous creatures.
在我们开始之前，让我们取消静音。
Before we begin, let's unmute.
现在是我们每天的舞蹈聚会的时间！
It is time for our daily dance party!
哦 没有人支持我
♪ Oh ♪ ♪ Nobody backs me up ♪
当我自己尝试，我m-m-mess it up
♪ When I try by myself, I m-m-mess it up ♪
哦，当他们说些什么？
♪ Oh ♪ ♪ Oh, when they say something ♪
哦，你总是吸起来
♪ Oh ♪ ♪ You always suck it up ♪
而当我试图帮助，它永远是不够的
♪ And when I try to help, it never is enough ♪
高五，高五。
High five, high five.
? 哦 ?
♪ Oh ♪
好了，让孩子们的早餐，使他们的午餐。
Okay, got the kids breakfast, made their lunches,
证实凯伦是我们13岁孩子的朋友
confirmed that Kaylen is our 13-year-old's friend
但不是朋友-朋友。
but not friend-friend.
轰隆隆。我统治。
Boom. I rule.
你还有什么给我的，拉蒙塔尼，嗯？
What else you got for me, LaMontagne, huh?
拿来吧。那么，你的胃口如何？
Bring it. Well, how's your appetite?
因为我今晚在那个新的意大利餐厅订了桌子。
'Cause I got us a table at that new Italian place tonight.
哦，意大利菜。
Ooh, Italiano.
是的。
Yeah.
今晚。
Tonight.
是的，今晚是约会之夜。
Yeah, tonight's date night.
今天早上又发现了一具尸体
Uh, another body turned up this morning.
石溪公园。
Rock Creek Park.
好吧。
Alright.
这是好的。
It's alright.
呃，嘿，坚持下去。
Uh, hey, hang on.
可能会有一些事情... ... 左右。
Might be able to shuffle some things... around.
不，不要这样做。
No, don't do that.
但你能不能，呃，为我确认一些事情？
But can you, uh, confirm something for me?
这样我就能告诉自己，我没有发疯？
So I can tell myself I'm not going crazy?
我们回来后，你肩上的担子很重。
You've had a lot on your shoulders since we got back.
就像，很多。
Like, a lot.
我知道你是超级妈妈，孩子们也没有受苦。
And I know you're supermom and the boys aren't suffering.
但是，嗯...
But, um...
嗯，你在说我们？
Um, you're talking about us?
是的。
Yeah.
算是吧。
Kinda.
好吧，只是...
Okay, just...
只要给我... 给我一个机会。
Just give me... Give me a chance.
好吗？弥补你的损失。
Alright? To make it up to you.
我会的。
I will.
我发誓。
I swear.
好的。
Okay.
祝你有个愉快的一天。
Have a good day.
早上好。你晚上过得怎么样？
Morning. How was your night?
很好，你呢？
Fine. How was yours?
很好
Good.
你，呃，还住在那个酒店外面，戴夫？
You, uh, still living out of that hotel, Dave?
那是什么案子？
What's the case?
这个是在我们的后院。
This one is in our backyard.
四天前，亚历克斯-阿诺德被扔在了
Four days ago, Alex Arnold was dumped
被扔在银泉镇外的一个休息站。
at a rest stop outside of Silver Spring.
死因是脊柱断裂。
Cause of death was a severed spinal cord.
昨天晚上，史蒂夫-邓肯也被连累了。
Last night, it went serial with Steve Duncan.
同样的COD，脊髓断裂。
Same COD, severed spinal cord.
都是30多岁的帅气男人。
Good-looking men in their 30s,
不是我们经常看到的受害者。
not a victimology we see a lot of.
他们通常是UnSubs。
They're usually the UnSubs.
好吧，这两个人被盯上了，有一个非常具体的原因。
Well, these two were targeted for a very specific reason.
他们都有像Tinder、Feeld这样的应用程序。
They both had apps like Tinder, Feeld,
他们的手机上有成人朋友搜索器。
Adult Friend Finder on their phone.
这就是他们为自己的服务做广告的地方，作为公牛。
That is where they advertise their services as bulls.
公牛和种马是一回事吗？
Are bulls the same thing as studs?
接近。
Close.
在被称为 "戴绿帽子 "的怪癖中，妻子对丈夫进行欺骗。
In the kink known as cuckolding,
妻子用公牛欺骗她们的丈夫。
wives cheat on their husbands with bulls.
男人喜欢这样。
Men like this.
没有金钱交易。
No money trades hands.
这都是合法的，而且是双方同意的。
It's all legal and consensual.
UnSub可能会因此被烧死。
The UnSub could have been burned by that.
现在他正在进行报复。
Now he's taking his revenge.
还有一个原因，我们必须接手这个案子。
There is another reason why we have to take this case.
我们的上一个UnSub，Rory Gilcrest，
Our last UnSub, Rory Gilcrest,
他在沃尔玛的一个停车场换了车。
he switched cars at a Wal-Mart parking lot.
这个UnSub也做了同样的事情。下到沃尔玛超市。
This UnSub did the same thing. Down to the Wal-Mart.
我们剖析，罗里有一个合作伙伴。
We profiled that Rory had a partner.
但是，我的意思是...
But, I mean...
这是我们的海运集装箱的家伙吗？
Is this our shipping container guy?
我跟Tara查过了
I checked with Tara.
集装箱里的尸体都没有
None of the bodies in the shipping container
都没有切断脊柱。
have severed spinal cords.
是的，这是一个非常特殊的签名。
Yes, this is a very specific signature,
但我们不能无视眼前的事实。
but we can't ignore what's in front of us.
我们上一个案子的细节在这里显示出来。
Details from our last case are showing up here.
那么还有一个我们必须考虑的理论。
Then there's another theory we have to consider.
这个集装箱背后的人
Who's ever behind the shipping container
并非只有一个伙伴。
doesn't have one partner.
他有两个。
He has two.
所以，这里的计划是标准操作程序。
So, the plan here is standard operating procedure.
我们正在处理这些照片。
We are processing the photographs,
但我们的主要重点是完整的DNA分解。
but our main focus is a complete DNA breakdown.
一旦样本被交叉和分型，
Once the samples are crossed and typed,
我们可以识别尸体，然后，手指交叉，我们的UnSub。
we can ID bodies and then, fingers crossed, our UnSub.
Locard的交换原则说，犯罪者在每个犯罪现场都会拿走和留下一些东西。
Locard's Exchange Principle says that a perpetrator
在每个犯罪现场都会带走和留下一些东西。
takes and leaves something at every crime scene.
如果这家伙17年来都在重访这个案子
If this guy revisited this for 17 years,
一定会有他的一部分在那里的
there's gonna be some piece of him in there.
Prentiss? 你做了什么?
Prentiss? What did you do?
贝利局长, 长官, 我不得不把它从华盛顿州转移过来。
Director Bailey, sir, I had to move this from Washington State.
当地人没有必要的资源
The locals didn't have the resources necessary
来全面调查它
to investigate it fully.
我也明白。我喜欢它。
And I get it. I love it.
我喜欢这种热情。
I love the enthusiasm.
但上级不会喜欢这样。
But the brass is not gonna like this.
尸体数量已经上升到24具。
The body count's already gone up to 24,
还没算上尸骨。
not counting the bones.
我想把话说清楚。
I-I want to be clear here.
上头不希望BAU来解决这个案子？
The brass doesn't want the BAU solving this case?
没那么简单。
It's not that simple.
让我把它放在旗杆上。
Let me run it up the flagpole.
希望它是值得的。
Just hope it's worth it.
给我接资源管理部的McNamara主任。
Get me Director McNamara in Resource Management.
伙计。你每天都在处理这个问题？
Man. You deal with that every day?
每一天。
Every day.
好像这工作还不够难似的。
As if this job wasn't hard enough.
我希望你仔细听好。
I want you to listen very carefully.
因为你要做一个选择。
Because you have a choice to make.
我将切断你的脊髓。
I'm going to cut your spinal cord.
哦，上帝。
Oh, God.
你可以选择以四肢瘫痪的方式生活。
You can either live as a quadriplegic.
从脖子以下什么都不能控制。
Control nothing from the neck down.
或者我杀了你。
Or I kill you.
那么你的选择是什么？
So what's your choice?
杀了我。
Kill me.
据称，奥斯卡-王尔德写道：
It is claimed that Oscar Wilde wrote,
"世界上的一切都与性有关，除了性。
"Everything in the world is about sex, except sex.
性是关于权力的。"
Sex is about power."
除了他没有。
Except he didn't.
没有人知道是谁写的。
Nobody knows who wrote it.
所以我梳理了我们两个受害者的手机。
So I combed through our two victims' cellphones.
还有，呃，这些公牛。
And, uh, these bulls,
他们让很多女人都非常非常开心。
they made a large number of women very, very happy.
你是什么人？ 嫉妒吗？不是。
What're you, jealous? No.
我太尊重婚姻的神圣性了
I respect the sanctity of marriage too much
不敢惹已婚妇女。
to mess with married women.
我在寻找妻子们之间的重叠部分。
I was looking for overlap between the wives.
如果UnSub是一个戴绿帽子的丈夫，
If the UnSub is a cuckolded husband,
我想这就是开始的地方，但到目前为止，什么都没有。
I figured that's the place to start, but so far, nothing.
毒物屏幕怎么样？
How about a tox screen?
这个UnSub说一定是在使用重型麻醉剂。
This UnSub said must be using heavy-duty narcotics.
还在等待。但你是对的。
Still waiting. But you're right.
如果他要做背部手术
If he's performing back surgery,
那就不能只在头上打一拳了
it's gonna take a lot more than a bonk on the head.
酒店的情况如何？
Where are we with hotels?
第一家没有帮助。
Number one was no help.
但二号有收据。
But number two had the receipts.
所以史蒂夫-邓肯没有支付房间的费用。
So Steve Duncan didn't pay for the room.
他的女性朋友付了，朱莉-沙利文。
His lady friend did, Julie Sullivan.
为什么她看起来很眼熟？
Why does she look familiar?
那是因为她嫁给了这个人。
That's 'cause she's married to this guy.
杰克-沙利文，哥伦比亚区的市议员。
Jack Sullivan, City Councilman for the District of Columbia.
把他们两个带进来。
Bring them both in.
那位议员会阻挠我们的。
The councilman will stonewall us,
但我们也许能从他妻子那里得到些什么。
but we might be able to get something from the wife.
如果我们能得到一些关于他们俩的背景资料就好了
It'd be nice if we could get some background intel
但没有佩内洛普...
on the both of them, but without Penelope...
我们没有时间了。
We don't have time.
伙计们，我知道BAU是不同的。
Guys, I know the BAU is different.
我想念Reid 我想Simmons
I miss Reid. I miss Simmons.
我们都想念佩内洛普
And we all miss Penelope.
但我们必须在没有他们的情况下解决这个案子。
But we're gonna have to solve this case without them.
好了，伙计们，你们都很好。
Okay, pals, you're all wonderful,
但这些小盒子却让我的大脑摇摇欲坠。
but these little boxes are making my brain wobbly.
我相信这不仅仅是我的问题。
And I'm sure it's not just me.
所以，我们明天再继续吧，好吗？
So let's pick this up tomorrow, okay?
佩内洛普，当我使用自动界面时，我仍然得到一个503
Penelope, I'm still getting a 503
当我使用自动界面时，我仍然得到503。
when I use the automated interface.
哦，莱利，我明白你的痛苦。
Oh, Riley, I feel your pain.
我告诉你吧。
I'll tell you what,
我会把我的诊断清单发给你。
I will e-mail you my diagnostic checklist.
还是不行，给我打电话。好吗？
Still no bueno, give me a call. Okay?
但不要在12点和1点之间
Except not between 12:00 and 1:00
因为那是我的野餐时间。
because that is my picnic time.
好吗？再见！
Alright? Bye!
再见！
Auf Wiedersehen!
这是谁？
Who is this?
你是谁，请问？
Who are you, please?
哦。
Oh.
听着，我不能帮你。
Look, I cannot help you.
你问我的事，会毁了我的事业。
What you're asking me about, it will destroy my career.
那就帮帮你自己吧，议员。
Then help yourself out, Councilman.
让我们从这里开始。
Let's start here.
你告诉我你昨天晚上在哪里。
You tell me where you were last night.
如果我们能证明你的故事，
And if we can back up your story,
那么你的私生活就能保持隐私。
then your private life stays private.
我在家里等待。
I was at home waiting.
为朱莉？
For Julie?
杰克在等我。
Jack waits for me.
当我和，你知道，其他男人在一起时，
And when I'm with, you know, other men,
我给他发视频。
I-I send him videos.
你这样做的时候，你丈夫不会吃醋吗？
Doesn't your husband get jealous when you do this?
生气吗？
Angry?
不会。
No.
这是我的主意。
It was my idea.
我不认为她会喜欢它，但是，呃... ...
I didn't think she would like it, but, uh...
我喜欢。
I do.
因为当他回家的时候，
Because when he comes home,
就像他必须再次赢得我的信任。
it's like he has to win me over again.
这不关我的事，好吗？
It's none of my business, okay?
我不是来让你感到羞愧的。
I'm not here to kink-shame you.
但我得说实话。
But I've got to be honest.
很多人都为小事而杀人。
A lot of men have killed over less.
那不是我。
That's not me.
我不是一个杀手。
I'm not a killer.
你能证明这一点吗？
Can you prove it?
有一个最后的视频，杰克得到了。
There's one last video Jack got.
我会让他给你看的。
I'll have him show it to you.
这是你和史蒂夫的录像吗？
Is it of you and Steve?
不是。
No.
是他给的。你要找的那个人。
It was from him. The man you're looking for.
我很抱歉。我知道我们应该早点站出来。
I'm sorry. I know we should have come forward sooner.
凶手给你发了一个视频？
The killer sent you a video?
等一下。等等，什么？你怎么知道的？
Wait a minute. Wait, what? H-How do you know?
你的妻子刚刚告诉我。
Your wife just told me.
我们需要你的手机，现在。
We need your phone right now.
我没办法。如果有人发现了...
I can't. I-If anyone finds out...
如果你不说，我们会逮捕你
If you don't, we'll arrest you
隐瞒重要证据的罪名
for withholding material evidence
在谋杀案调查中隐瞒重要证据。
in a homicide investigation.
你知道那时会发生什么吗？
You know what happens then?
每个人都会发现的。
Everyone finds out.
你不会是认真的吧。
You can't be serious.
我只是个传话人。
I'm just the messenger.
但上级领导说得很清楚。
But the higher-ups were very clear.
所有与移动集装箱有关的费用
All costs associated with moving the shipping container
从BAU的预算中支出。
come out of the BAU's budget.
主任，恕我直言，
Director, with all due respect,
这个团队已经完成了你所要求的一切。
this team has done everything you've asked.
我们少花钱多办事，我们节衣缩食，我们节省了。
We've done more with less, we've scrimped, we've saved.
而且作为科长
And as section chief,
我被允许自由支配的开支。
I am allowed discretionary spending.
我提出了这个观点。
I made that point.
他们说你没有那么多自由裁量权。
They said you don't have that much discretion.
我很抱歉，艾米丽。
I'm sorry, Emily.
我们不可能赢过豆类计算员的。
We can't win against the bean counters.
真是一派胡言。
What a crock of shit.
这就像我们正在被惩罚，因为我们的工作做得好。
It's like we're being punished for being good at our job.
你认识Rebecca Wilson吗？
Do you know Rebecca Wilson?
在DOJ？认识。她是我的朋友。
At the DOJ? Yeah. She's a friend.
要不要我让她去打听一下，看看有什么事？
Want me to have her ask around, find out what's up?
上帝，是的，请。
God, yes, please.
请告诉我，我们在集装箱方面获得了突破。
And please tell me we caught a break with the container.
我希望我可以。
I wish I could.
我们已经覆盖了每一个角落，对每一具尸体进行了拭擦。
We have covered every corner, swabbed every corpse.
我们三番五次地检查了那个鞋柜。
We triple-checked that foot locker.
什么都没有。
Nothing.
洛克德可以吻我的屁股。
Locard can kiss my ass.
来吧。没有人是那么好的。
Come on. Nobody's that good.
你想打赌吗？
You want to bet?
他在金属上做了两次，有时甚至三次加固
He double- and sometimes triple-reinforced the metal
以防止渗漏。
to prevent leaks.
他用漂白剂擦拭了每个表面
He wiped down every surface with bleach
以破坏第三方的DNA。
to destroy third-party DNA.
他希望这个地方尽可能地密不透风。
He wanted this place as airtight as possible.
安全，可靠。
Safe, secure.
如果这些尸体是战利品，就像你想的那样。
If the bodies were trophies, like you thought,
他想尽可能长时间地保存它们。
he'd want to preserve them as long as possible.
你知道，我确实这么想。
You know, I-I did think that.
但现在我认为它们是实验品。
But now I think they were experiments,
因为他从不重复相同的模式。
because he never repeated the same pattern.
我是说，他刺伤了那个人，射杀了她，勒死了他。
I mean, he stabbed that guy, shot her, strangled him.
然后是这个人。
And then there's this guy.
他对这个人做了什么？
What did he do to this guy?
他把Sicarius蜘蛛倒进这个受害者的喉咙。
He poured Sicarius spiders down this victim's throat.
它们是一个令人难以置信的有毒的属种
They're an incredibly poisonous genus
与棕色隐士有关。
related to the brown recluse.
一些实验室的技术人员开始
Some of the lab techs are starting
开始把这只 "不明生物 "叫做 "西卡利斯"。
to call this UnSub that, "Sicarius."
我讨厌蜘蛛。
I hate spiders.
是的。
Yeah.
好吧，看起来像JJ和Alvez有一个突破，在他们的案件，
Okay, looks like JJ and Alvez had a break in their case,
但他们需要和整个团队谈谈，包括你。
but they need to talk to the entire team, including you.
你可以选择以四肢瘫痪的方式生活。
You can either live as a quadriplegic.
脖子以下什么都不能控制。
Control nothing from the neck down.
或者我杀了你。
Or I kill you.
那么你的选择是什么？
So what's your choice?
瘫痪或死亡。
Paralyzation or death.
给予史蒂夫-邓肯一个不可能的选择
Giving Steve Duncan an impossible choice
只会加剧UnSub的虐待狂。
only heightens the UnSub's sadism.
他露出了他的脸吗？
Does he reveal his face?
没有，但他确实透露了一些别的东西
No, but he does reveal something else
在他关闭视频的时候。
as he's turning the video off.
对...。
Right...
这里。
here.
哇。这是另一个杀人工具。
Whoa. That's another kill kit.
是的。我们认为这些案件有联系...
Yeah. We thought these cases were connected...
那个集装箱，Rory Gilcrest。
The shipping container, Rory Gilcrest,
脊柱的家伙。
our spinal cord guy.
现在我们有了确凿的证据
And now we have our smoking gun.
嗯。
Hmm.
戴夫，你在想什么？
Dave, what are you thinking?
我做了这么多年的侧写员
All my years as a profiler,
我研究过各种压力下的杀手。
I studied killers under all kinds of pressure.
但我从未研究过大流行病会对他们造成什么影响。
But I never studied what a pandemic would do to them.
他们不能移动，不能狩猎。
They couldn't move, they couldn't hunt.
但这种强迫性仍会驱使他们。
But that compulsion would still drive them,
而且他们需要某种出口。
and they would need some sort of an outlet.
所以它们开始交流。
So they started communicating,
互相帮助，使之成为更好的捕食者。
helping each other to become better predators.
我们已经有了两个。
We've got two.
如果我们跟着面包屑走，我们会找到第三个。
And if we follow the bread crumbs, we'll find our third.
不，不，不。这太有组织了，太有联系了。
No, no, no. This is too organized, too connected.
还有更多。
There's more.
我们还不确定。
We don't know that for sure.
想想我们到目前为止对他的了解。
Think about what we do know about him so far.
他是有控制的，有纪律的。
He's controlled, disciplined.
他知道如何隐藏。对吗？
He knows how to hide. Right?
他知道如果没有尸体，就没有犯罪。
He knows if there's no body, there's no crime.
但他是个猎人，不安分。
But he's a hunter, restless.
总是在寻找一个更好的方法。
Always looking for a better way.
所以让我们把这种行为运用到他的追随者身上。
So let's apply that behavior to his followers.
我明白罗西的意思。
I see what Rossi's saying.
为什么他只满足于两个人？
Why would he be content with just two?
他并不满足于这些杀戮。
He isn't with the killings.
所以这些不只是有联系的案件。
So these aren't just connected cases.
这是个网络。
This is a network.
我不明白
I don't understand.
为什么我们不能告诉贝利局长我们所掌握的情况？
Why can't we tell Director Bailey what we have?
因为这还不够。你怎么能这样说呢？
Because it's not enough. How can you say that?
这是我们有史以来最大的案子了
This is the biggest case we've ever had.
好吧，那么我们就坚持我们能证明的东西。
O-Okay, so let's just stick to what we can prove.
我们认为海运集装箱在2020年结束
We thought the shipping container ended in 2020
因为大流行病，但事实并非如此。
because of the pandemic, but it didn't.
相反，UnSub聚集了追随者。
Instead, the UnSub gathered followers.
他现在正在激活的追随者。
Followers that he's now activating.
如果这就是他的乐趣所在
And if that's what he gets off on,
他可能会重新激活自己。
he might reactivate himself.
伊斯雷尔-凯伊斯在全国各地放置了杀人工具。
Israel Keyes placed kill kits across the country,
都是为他自己所用。
all for his own use.
艾米丽，我们需要更多的资源。你知道这一点。
Emily, we need more resources. You know that.
我也知道，每次我试图获得这些资源时，
I also know that every time I try to get those resources,
贝利就会耍我们。
Bailey screws us.
我们需要的是一个绕过他的方法。
What we need is a way around him.
有什么想法吗？
Have any ideas?
没有。
No.
但她可能有。
But she might.
Prentiss, Rossi, 我是司法部的Rebecca Wilson.
Prentiss, Rossi, this is Rebecca Wilson with the DOJ.
嗨, Emily.
Hi, Emily.
Rossi探员, 我是你的粉丝
Agent Rossi, big fan.
如果你能让一些FBI的官僚们离开我们，也是同样的道理。
Likewise if you can get some FBI bureaucrats off our back.
我拿到了关于Bailey局长的下载。
I got the download on Director Bailey.
他通过成为效率专家在司法部爬上了阶梯。
He climbed the ladder at DOJ by being an efficiency expert.
削减预算，减少人员，有功劳就拿，没功劳就推。
Slashes budgets, reduces staff, takes the credit when he can,
并在其他地方推卸责任。
and passes the buck everywhere else.
现在，他是该局的副局长。
Now that he's Deputy Director for the Bureau,
他看到了一条成为总检察长的道路。
he sees a path to becoming AG.
所以BAU是一个政治足球。
So the BAU's a political football.
更像是一个棋子。
More like a chess piece.
解释给我听，就像我是五岁小孩一样。
Explain something to me like I'm five.
该单位得到的结果。
The unit gets results.
别人看到的是怪物，我们看到的是模式。
Where others see monsters, we see patterns.
我们了解精神病患者的思维方式，我们阻止他们。
We understand how psychopaths think and we stop them.
为什么要修复没有损坏的东西？
Why fix what's not broken?
我可以四处打听。
I can ask around.
桌子上没有任何东西。
There's nothing on the table.
但可能有一些事情正在进行中。
But there could be something in the works.
总有一些东西在工作中。
There's always something in the works.
谢谢你，丽贝卡。是啊。
Thanks, Rebecca. Yeah.
你在跟我开玩笑吗？你在开玩笑吗？
Are you kidding me? Are you kidding?
嗷。什么？
Ow. What?
你 -你和她。
Y-You and her.
你们是一对。
You're so a thing.
不！什么？
No! W-What?
哦，天哪。有那么明显吗？
Oh, God. Is it that obvious?
我的意思是，房间里的温度上升了
I mean, the temperature in the room went up
你们两个进来的时候，温度上升了10度。
like 10 degrees when you two walked in.
这事发生多久了？
How long has this been going on?
几个月了。桌子上的牌。
A couple months. Cards on the table.
这不是我第一次和一个女人约会。
This is not my first time dating a woman,
但是，哦，伙计，
but, oh, man,
这是我第一次这么开心。
it is my first time being this happy.
哦，那很好。
Oh, that's good.
哦，我们可以使用一些快乐在这里。
Oh, we could use some happiness around here.
此外，我们会给你这么多的狗屎。
Besides, we're gonna give you so much shit for this.
唉。
Ugh.
怎么了？
What is it?
我什么时候能再去？
When do I get to go again?
我告诉过你。还没有。
I told you. Not yet.
这不公平。有一个人是我想要的。
That's not fair. There's someone I want.
罗伯特，你是在违抗我的命令吗？
Robert, are you disobeying me?
不，当然不是。
No, of course not.
但为什么我们现在要停下来？
But why are we stopping now?
这不是一个停止。是暂停。
It's not a stop. It's a pause.
有人拿走了我的东西。
Somebody took something of mine.
我需要确保这不会再发生。
I need to make sure that can't happen again.
然后你就可以再去了。
And then you can go again.
什么时候？
When?
很快。
Soon.
我得先去买点东西。
I need to do some shopping first.
好的，那是10卷胶带。
Okay, that's 10 rolls of duct tape,
6卷电工胶带，10个拨动开关。
6 rolls of electrical tape, 10 toggle switches,
4袋电线螺母，剪线钳。
4 bags of wire nuts, wire cutters,
2个12伏的小电池。
2 small 12-volt batteries.
这将是449.49美元。
That'll be $449.49.
你收现金吗？
Do you take cash?
当然。
Sure.
对不起。必须确保你不是一个造假者
Sorry. Got to make sure you're not a counterfeiter
或毒贩。
or drug dealer.
绝对不是那么有趣。
Definitely not that interesting.
呃，网络安全，你知道，
Uh, network security, you know,
确保人们不被黑客攻击，诸如此类的事情。
making sure people don't get hacked, that sort of thing.
你在网络安全方面需要胶带？
You need duct tape for network security?
不，我需要胶带来做一个个人项目
No, I need duct tape for a personal project
因为网络安全是非常无聊的。
that engages my mind because network security is very boring.
特别是在大流行期间。
Especially during the pandemic.
你会震惊于人们的粗心大意。
You'd be shocked how careless people get
当你通过互联网给他们指示时。
when you give them instructions over the Internet.
看看我工作的地方。
Look where I work.
我完全可以相信它。
I can totally believe it.
嘿，你可以得到这个。这很好。
Hey, you can get that. It's fine.
不。工作。它总是工作。
Nah. Work. It's always work.
不用担心。
Don't worry about it.
你想加入我们的奖励计划吗？
Did you want to join our rewards program?
不，我很好。你确定？
No, I'm good. You sure?
因为，我的意思是，你得到20％的折扣，你有一个巨大的订单。
'Cause, I mean, you get 20% off and you have a huge order.
我说我很好！
I said I'm good!
嗯，我的错。
Um, my bad.
对不起。
Sorry.
那是谁？
Who's that?
啊，那是Moose。
Ah, that's Moose.
他是我的小伙伴。
He's my floof.
你知道，网络安全，家庭安全。
You know, network security, home security,
我们携手并进。
we work hand in hand.
安全摄像机，运动感应灯。
Security cameras, motion-sensor lights.
这都是一样的。没有什么能胜过一条狗。
It's all the same. Nothing beats a dog.
麋鹿不是。他是一个大的老笨蛋。
Not Moose. He's a big old goofball.
你不觉得吗？
You don't say?
嗯，嗯。
Mm-hmm.
好吧，托尼，谢谢你做的一切。
Well, Tawny, thank you for everything.
如果有一天谁在管理网络的时候和加西亚一样好呢？
What if who's ever running the network is as good as Garcia?
你知道吗，我们的脊梁骨医生
You know, our spinal-cord guy
知道Sullivans家的電話號碼
knew the Sullivans' phone number.
他知道他们何时何地与他们的公牛见面。
He knew when and where they were meeting their bulls.
到目前为止，我们的远程Garcias没有发现什么。
So far, our remote Garcias have found nothing.
如果Sicarius和他的追随者在黑客方面和谋杀方面一样出色
If Sicarius and his followers are as good at hacking
我们就有麻烦了
as they are at murder, we're in trouble.
谁是Sicarius?
Who's Sicarius?
呃 Tara说他们给那个集装箱命名为
Uh, Tara said that's what they're naming
船运集装箱UnSub
the shipping container UnSub.
我才不会给这个垃圾箱起名字呢
I'm not gonna name this jag-off.
笨蛋! 好吗？就这么叫他。
Fuckhead! Okay? Call him that.
我想知道如何抓住他。
I want to know how to catch him.
就像我们抓捕恐怖组织或黑手党一样
Go about that the same way we would a terrorist cell
或者黑手党家族，对吗？
or a Mafia family, right?
一次一个案子，希望我们的UnSub能给我们整个网络。
One case at a time and hope that our UnSub
希望我们的UnSub能给我们整个网络。
gives us the whole network.
好吧，那么让我们专注于这个案子。
Well, then let's focus on this case.
我们的情况如何？
Where are we with the profile?
在嫉妒的丈夫方面还是没有进展。
Still nowhere on the jealous-husband front.
我的意思是，我询问过的那些人，
I mean, the guys that I questioned,
他们都是beta型男性，非暴力型。
they're all beta males, nonviolent type.
我开始觉得
I'm beginning to think
我们在寻找错误的嫌疑人。
we're looking in the wrong suspect pool.
是的，我也这么认为。
Yeah, I am, too.
特别是在看了那个谋杀视频之后。
Especially after watching that murder video.
好吧，那么给丈夫发送自制的色情制品
Okay, so sending the husband homemade porn
是绿帽子的一部分，对不对？
is part of the cuckold kink, right?
公牛对权力和控制感到兴奋。
The bull gets off on the power and control.
这就是为什么我们的资料被关闭了。
That's why our profile's off.
如果我们在理论的基础上重新建立档案
If we rebuild the profile based around the theory
它是一头公牛杀死其他公牛。
that it's a bull killing other bulls,
我想我们会走得更远。
I think we'll get farther.
做吧。
Do it.
佩内洛普？
Penelope?
我需要见你。
Garcia: I need to see you.
我不知道是什么事。
I don't know what it is.
只是联邦调查局调查中的重要证据。
Just material evidence in an FBI investigation.
然而，还有13个加密链接
However, 13 additional encryption links
嵌入在那里。
are embedded in there.
我猜是更多的坐标，但MNH。
My guess is it's more coordinates, but mnh.
你应该让那些不如我的人去破解它。
You should have the me's-who- are-not-as-good-as-me crack it.
这有点可疑，你不觉得吗？
That's kind of suspicious, don't you think?
我是说，有人在我们发现一个连环杀手网络的同一天给你发了邮件
I mean, somebody e-mails this to you on the same day
我们发现了一个连环杀手网络?
that we uncover a serial killer network?
可疑的，巧合的，不是我的部门了。
Suspicious, coincidence, not my department anymore.
好吧，也许它应该是。
Well, maybe it ought to be,
因为这已经是他们第二次把你拉进来了
'cause this is the second time they've pulled you in.
现在有人在给你提供线索。
And now somebody is feeding you clues.
我们需要你把事情查个水落石出。
We need you to get to the bottom of this.
嗯。
Mm.
什么？
What?
没什么。
Nothing.
没有。 嘿，嘿，嘿。
No. Hey, hey, hey.
什么？不，等等。你可以告诉我。
What? No, wait. You can tell me.
跟我说话。什么？
Talk to me. What?
克劳特死后你去治疗了吗？
Have you gone to therapy since Krystall died?
这到底是什么意思？
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
你说我可以说的。是啊，好吧，好吧。
You said I could say it. Yeah, well, alright.
好吧，这有点评判性，你不觉得吗？
Well, that's a little judgy, don't you think?
我没有评判。我认为你是。
I am not judgy. I think that you are.
我将以我自己的方式悲伤。非常感谢你。
I'll grieve in my own way. Thank you very much.
我希望其他人能尊重这一点。
And I wish other people would respect that.
我是这么想的。我确实尊重它。
I do. I do respect it.
只是，我一直在接受治疗，好吗？
It's just that I've been going to therapy, okay?
而且... 而其中一件事
And... And one of the things
我的持牌临床社会工作者崔斯坦帮助我看到
that my licensed clinical social worker, Tristan, helped me see
在他们把下巴从地上捡起来之后
after they picked their jaw up off the floor
从了解到我所经历的所有事情后。
from learning of all the things I've survived,
我从很小的时候就一直在吸收心理创伤
I have been absorbing trauma since I was really young
并认为我是某种英雄的做法。
and thinking I was some sort of hero for doing it.
然后我找了一份工作，做了15年
And then I got a job for 15 years
即使你做了正确的事情，
where even when you do the right thing,
甚至当你阻止连环杀手时，
even when you stop serial killers,
你的身体正在吸收这种创伤。
your body is absorbing that trauma.
我并不是一个坚持不懈的英雄。
And I'm not a hero for holding on to it
因为创伤必须被卸下。
because trauma has to be off-loaded.
它必须被转化，否则你的身体会摧毁你。
It has to be transformed, or your body will destroy you.
而戴夫，当我看着你...
And Dave, when I look at you...
自从你发现了克洛特的诊断结果后...
ever since you found out about Krystall's diagnosis...
我想我们最好不要去那里。
I think it's better we don't go there.
好吧 好的。
Right. Okay.
我的意思是，你知道在大流行病期间，每个人的生活如何
What I mean is, you know how everybody's life
在大流行病期间分崩离析
fell apart during the pandemic
但也有少数人
but then there was a handful of people
但却有一小部分人因就地避难而生活得很好？
that were thriving from sheltering in place?
我就是这些人中的一个。
I am one of those people.
我的静息心率很高。
My resting heart rate is stellar.
我正在吃更多的植物营养素。
I'm eating even more phytonutrients.
我在冥想。
I-I'm meditating.
你应该试试，实际上。
You should try that, actually.
我试过。我一直睡着了。
I did. I kept falling asleep.
我也是。那是发生在我身上的事。
Me too. That was happening to me.
你需要... 不是问题的关键。
You need to... Not the point.
我现在的重点是，我每天都想念这个团队。
My point right now is, I miss the team every day.
我每天都想念你。
I miss you every day.
但我不想念工作。
But I don't miss the work.
我可以给你一个拥抱吗，这样我就知道我们没事了？
Can I give you a hug so I know we're okay?
我把你的沉默当作同意。
I'm gonna take your silence as consent.
这就是我对人的简介。
This is how I profile people.
我真的很为你高兴。
I really am happy for you.
不仅如此，我还很嫉妒。
More than that, I'm jealous.
我想要你拥有的东西。
I want what you have.
但现在我有个工作要做。
But right now I've got a job to do.
你得去抓一个坏人。
You got to go catch a bad guy.
啊，不，帮助！
Aah! No! Help!
这次他带走了一个女人？
He took a woman this time?
我们确定是同一个UnSub吗？
Are we sure it's the same UnSub?
是的。米歇尔-塔克。
Yeah. Michelle Tucker.
住在马里兰州的弗雷德里克。
Lives in Frederick, Maryland.
她的丈夫报告说她失踪了。
Her husband reported her missing.
警方在一家好市多发现了她被遗弃的汽车。
Police found her abandoned car at a Costco.
不是沃尔玛，但足够接近。
Not a Wal-Mart, but close enough.
这是受害者研究中的一个巨大转变。
That's a huge shift in victimology.
为什么现在改变？
Why change now?
我想是因为他不得不这样做。
I'm thinking because he had to.
我们得到了毒物筛查的结果。
We got the tox screen results back,
还有他用来做手术的药物。
and the drugs that he uses for the surgeries,
他们是麻痹剂，用来固定受害者的身体，没错。
they're paralytics to immobilize the victim, sure,
但它们通常是用来
but they're typically prescribed
但通常是用来治疗背部受伤的疼痛。
to treat pain from a back injury.
因此，如果这种药物是他的。
So if this medication is his,
他的情况可以告诉我们一些关于他的信息。
his condition could tell us something about him.
一个有背伤的人只能携带这么多200磅重的人
There's only so many 200-pound men
一个有背伤的人可以随身携带的东西。
a guy with a back injury can carry around.
所以他服用了米歇尔。
So he took Michelle.
也许那是出于方便。
Maybe that was out of convenience,
但我们不能排除有个人关系。
but we can't rule out a personal connection.
这就像他的癖好被翻了出来。
It's like his kink got turned inside out.
你是什么意思？
What do you mean?
背部受伤的一个副作用是勃起功能障碍。
One side effect of back injuries is erectile dysfunction.
我们的恐惧会在我们的性生活中表现出来。
Our fears come out in our sex lives.
我们不愿意承认，但这是事实。
We hate to admit it, but it's true.
他不能再表演了。
He can't perform anymore.
所以他在惩罚那些仍然可以的人。
So he's punishing anyone who still can.
切断脊髓是他感受到阳刚之气的唯一途径。
Severing the spinal cord is his only way to feel virile.
丈夫在来的路上吗？
Is the husband on his way in?
是的。刚刚落地。
Yeah. Just landed.
把我们的资料给他。
Give him our profile.
不知何故，他和米歇尔认识这个人。
Somehow he and Michelle know this guy.
不，不，这不可能发生。
No, no, this can't be happening.
塔克先生，我们已经尽力了。
Mr. Tucker, we're doing everything we can,
但我们最大的希望取决于你在这里完全诚实。
but our best hope depends on you being completely honest here.
是的，是的，无论你需要什么。
Yeah, yeah, whatever you need.
米歇尔昨天晚上和谁在一起？
Who was Michelle seeing last night?
这个人。
This guy.
等一下。那是同一个号码
Wait a minute. That's the same number
发送视频给Sullivans的那个号码。
that sent the video to the Sullivans.
我要在这里做一个反向图片搜索。
Gonna do a reverse image search here.
这是从一个性感的消防员日历。
This is from a sexy firefighters calendar.
你和Michelle被骗了。
You and Michelle were catfished.
什么？
What?
塔克先生，米歇尔被盯上是有原因的。
Mr. Tucker, Michelle was targeted for a reason.
也许是因为你以前见过这头牛。
Maybe because you'd seen this bull before.
一个最近背部受伤的人
A man who recently suffered a back injury
他不能再表演了。
who can't perform anymore.
这有什么印象吗？
Does any of this ring a bell?
罗伯特-哈里斯。
Robert Harris.
好的。
Okay.
他是谁？
Who is he?
他承诺过米歇尔会有最好的性生活。
He promised the best sex Michelle was ever gonna have.
但几个月前，他遇到了一场摩托车事故，
But a couple months ago, he got into a motorcycle accident,
所以我们找到了另一个公牛。
so we found another bull.
在伤口上撒盐。
Salt in the wound.
告诉他他还不够好。
Telling him he's not good enough.
他就会攻击这个。
He'd attack that.
好的，我们需要你掌握的关于他的一切信息。
Okay, we need everything you have on him.
电话号码，地址，汽车，任何东西。是的。
Phone number, address, car, anything. Yeah.
你可能会感到侵入性的想法。
You might feel intrusive thoughts.
这是很自然的。
That's perfectly natural.
只要观察这些想法。
Just observe those thoughts.
就像一根树枝漂浮在溪流上。
Like a twig floating on a stream.
什么事，莱利？你还好吗？
Yeah, Riley? How are you?
莱利？
Riley?
HelperCat 220？
HelperCat 220?
是的，是的？
Y-Yes?
你解密了吗？
Did you decrypt it?
哦，我的上帝，是你。
Oh, my God, it's you.
你解密了吗？
Did you decrypt it?
没有，我是说，有，但没有。
No. I mean, yes, but no.
为什么没有？
Why not?
因为我把它交给了FBI。
Because I gave it to the FBI.
你说什么？把它给了FBI
You what? Gave it to the FBI.
听着，不管你认为我是谁，我不是。
Look, whoever you think I am, I am not.
那你是谁？你不明白吗？
Then who are you? Don't you understand?
你是唯一能帮助我的人。
You're the only one who could help me.
现在，因为你没有，人们就会死！
Now, because you didn't, people are gonna die!
喂？
H-Hello?
拜托，我不... 我不知道这是什么。
P-Please, I-I don... I don't know what this is.
为什么我不能动？
Why can't I move?
你感觉到了吗？没有。
Do you feel that? No.
你为什么要这样对我？
Why are you doing this to me?
因为你需要了解谁在负责。
Because you need to learn who's in charge.
你需要我的登录名或密码...
Do you need my login or passwo...
嗯。
Huh.
什么？
What?
每个链接都有一个不同的密钥。
Each link has a different key.
这意味着每一个人都会有不同的收件人。
That means each one goes to a different recipient.
总共13个。
13 in all.
你能破解它吗？
Can you crack it?
请你把这个打开好吗？
Can you turn this on, please?
把音量调到最大。
Turn the volume all the way up.
♪这节拍是我的朗诵会♪
♪ This beat is my recital ♪
我想这是非常重要的
♪ I think it's very vital ♪
摇滚的韵律，是正确的时间
♪ To rock a rhyme that's right on time ♪
标题是 "棘手"，我们开始吧
♪ It's Tricky is the title, here we go ♪
"摇摆不定的韵律很棘手
♪ It's tricky to rock a rhyme ♪
要摇动一个韵律，这是正确的时间
♪ To rock a rhyme that's right on time ♪
"这很棘手
♪ It's tricky ♪
狡猾，狡猾，狡猾，狡猾
♪ It's tricky, tricky, tricky, tricky ♪
摇摆押韵是件棘手的事
♪ It's tricky to rock a rhyme ♪
要摇动一个韵律的正确时间
♪ To rock a rhyme that's right on time ♪
"这很棘手
♪ It's tricky ♪
狡猾，狡猾，狡猾
♪ Tr-Tr-Tr-Tricky, tricky, trrricky ♪
我遇到了这个小姑娘
♪ I met this little girlie ♪
她的头发是有点卷曲
♪ Her hair was kinda curly ♪
*去了她家，把她弄出来*
♪ Went to her house and bust her out ♪
我不得不提前离开
♪ I had to leave real early ♪
这些女孩真的很狡猾
♪ These girls are really sleazy ♪
所有他们只是说，"请我"
♪ All they just say is, "Please me" ♪
或者花一些时间和摇滚的韵律
♪ Or spend some time and rock a rhyme ♪
我说 "这不是那么容易"
♪ I said "It's not that easy" ♪
它是棘手的摇滚韵律
♪ It's tricky to rock a rhyme ♪
要摇动一个正确的韵律...
♪ To rock a rhyme that's right on... ♪
我们在看什么呢？
What are we looking at?
我不知道。但我说我们要绘制它。
I don't know. But I say we map it.
棘手的，棘手的，棘手的，棘手的
♪ It's tricky, tricky, tricky, tricky ♪
"摇摆不定的韵律是很棘手的
♪ It's tricky to rock a rhyme ♪
震撼的韵律
♪ To rock a rhyme ♪
安静点，伙计们。
Quiet, guys.
什么事，塔拉？
Yeah, Tara?
杀人工具里的东西刚刚启动了
Something in the kill kit just went active.
那些是应答器。
Those are transponders.
UnSubs就是这样
This is how the UnSubs
找到他埋藏的杀人工具。
are finding they kill kits he's burying.
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
是的，因为JJ和Alvez
Yeah, because JJ and Alvez
现在正朝着一个方向前进。
are heading for one right now.
所有单位，所有单位，请注意。
All units, all units, be advised,
注意罗伯特-哈里斯。
be on the lookout for Robert Harris,
因与多起谋杀案有关而被通缉
wanted in association with multiple murders
和米歇尔-塔克的绑架案。
and the abduction of Michelle Tucker.
你不需要这样做。
You don't have to do this.
好吗？
Okay?
不管我做了什么，我... 我很抱歉。
Whatever I did, I'm... I'm sorry.
什么？
What?
你违反了规则，罗伯特。
You broke the rules, Robert.
不，我没有。
No, I didn't.
我让你暂停，你却没有。
I told you to pause, and you didn't.
我让你在第二地点工作，而你没有。
I told you to work from a secondary location,
而你没有。
and you didn't.
你知道我怎么知道的吗？
And do you know how I know that?
因为那该死的嘟嘟声
Because of the fucking beeping
我们现在都在听！
that we are both hearing right now!
我，我没有这样做。我不知道那是怎么发生的。
I-I didn't do this. I don't know how that happened.
我知道。你太马虎了。
I do. You got sloppy.
而现在警察正在去找你的路上。
And now the police are on their way to you.
而你知道这意味着什么。
And you know what that means.
我不能。
I-I can't.
好吧，如果你不能，那么我会的。
Well, if you can't, then I will.
现在，让我给你讲讲。
Now, let me talk you through it.
罗伯特-哈里斯自杀了。和Rory Gilcrest一样
Robert Harris killed himself. Same as Rory Gilcrest.
就像Rory一样 他没有任何自杀的迹象
And just like Rory, nothing about him profiled as suicidal.
不管Sicarius是谁，他一定有这些人的资料。
Whoever Sicarius is, he must have something on these guys.
或者这就是加入网络的 "魔鬼交易"。
Or that's the Devil's Bargain for joining the network.
在你被抓之前自杀。
Kill yourself before you get caught.
对他有好处 对我们不利
Good for him. Bad for us.
我们刚刚失去了最好的线索
We just lost our best lead.
没关系的。我们还有其他人。
It's okay. We've got others.
我们有吗？
We do?
我来解释。
I'll explain.
先去采访他们，这样他们就可以回家了。
Go interview them first so they can go home.
嘿，伙计们。
Hey, guys.
这可不好。
This is bad.
斗牛鲨可以生活在咸水和淡水中。
Bull sharks can live in both salt and fresh water.
嗨，宝贝。到这里来。它的食物包括鱼，
Hi, baby. Come here. Its diet consists of fish,
黄貂鱼，甲壳类动物。嗨。
stingrays, crustaceans. Hi.
麋鹿，好孩子!
Moose, good boy!
其他小鲨鱼种类。
Other small shark species.
牛头鲨喜欢在阴暗的水域中独自狩猎
The bull shark prefers to hunt by itself in murky waters
这样它的猎物就无法看到它。
so its prey is unable to see it.
它通常利用...
It commonly utilizes...
13个信号刚到12个。
13 signals just went to 12.
11. 搞什么鬼？
11. What the hell?
我们把它们打开了，现在又有人把它们关掉了。
We turned them on, and now someone turned them off,
这意味着他知道我们在盯着他。
which means he knows that we're on to him.
我只是让事情变得更糟了吗？
Did I just make things worse?
没有。
No.
你做了你一直做的事。
You did what you always do.
你帮了忙。
You helped.
没有我，你能阻止他们吗？
Can you stop them without me?
说实话？
Honestly?
我不知道。
I don't know.
我需要点时间。
I need a moment.
是的。我是罗西先生，1805室。
Yeah. This is Mr. Rossi, Room 1805.
我要去退房了。
I'm gonna be checking out.
谢谢。
Thanks.
你回来了
You're home.
是的，我不想吵醒你。
Yeah. I didn't want to wake you.
你什么时候进来的？刚到。
When'd you get in? Just now.
我错过了转机。我很幸运能搭上飞机。
I missed my connecting. I'm lucky I got a flight in.
你想让我给你倒杯酒吗？不用了，我很好。
You want me to pour you a cup? No, I'm good.
我的油箱里有足够的油，可以给女儿们做早餐。
I got enough gas in the tank to make breakfast for the girls.
然后我就去睡大觉。等等，你确定吗？
Then I'll hit the hay. Wait, are you sure?
因为这将是一个非常大的帮助。
Because that would be a really big help.
是的，我确定。
Yeah, sure I'm sure.
哦。
Aww.
有史以来最好的丈夫。
Best husband ever.
孩子们都出门了，所以我要去上班了。
The boys are out the door, so I'm gonna head into work.
呃，好的。谢谢。
Uh, yeah. Thanks.
你还好吗？
You doing alright?
你认为我们的恐惧会在我们的性生活中表现出来吗？
Do you think our fears come out in our sex life?
我有麻烦了吗？
Am I in trouble?
没有。
No.
那就好。
That's good.
我有时会想到我们的生活，
I think about our life sometimes,
我意识到，我们能做到这一点是很疯狂的。
and I realize it's crazy that we ever made it.
而现在我们的整个现实就是这个巨大的时钟
And now our whole reality is this giant clock
倒数着放学的时间
counting down the seconds between school drop-off
和... ...和家庭晚餐和...
and... and family dinners and...
死尸。
Dead bodies.
是的，那也是。
Yeah, that too.
而事实是，时间不够。
And the truth is, there isn't enough time.
从来就没有。
There never is.
而这...
And that...
这是我的恐惧。
That's my fear.
我们有全职工作和两个孩子。
We have full-time jobs and two kids.
我们正在尽力而为。
We're doing the best we can.
也许吧。
Maybe.
也许我们可以做得更好。
Maybe we could do better.
如果我们不能...
If we can't...
做好约会之夜...
make date night...
我们总是可以做约会的早晨。
we could always do date morning.
早晨。
Morning.
很高兴你回来了。
Glad you're back.
我从未离开过。
I never left.
你好。我们怎么样了？
Hello. How are we doing?
你看起来很好。
You look great.
哦，来吧。什么？
Oh, come on. What?
除了我，这里的每个人都在做爱吗？
Is everybody around here getting laid except me?
嗯，我没有。
Well, I'm not.
哇。我很抱歉。
Wow. I'm sorry.
胆小鬼的幽默，但这是我现在唯一的办法。
Gallows humor, but it's all I've got right now.
你知道吗？我愿意接受绞刑架式的幽默，而不是毫无幽默感。
You know what? I will take gallows humor over no humor.
我们有什么？
What do we have?
Tara的女朋友需要告诉我们一些
Tara's girlfriend needs to tell us something
关于Bailey主任的事
about Director Bailey.
好消息还是坏消息？
Good news or bad news?
等等，你说女朋友？
Wait, did you say girlfriend?
嘿，我们能不能，呃，把门关上？
Hey, can we, uh, close the door?
我要告诉你的事是机密。
What I'm about to tell you is classified.
如果有人发现是我说的，我就会被解雇。
If anyone finds out this came from me, I'll be fired.
明白了。
Understood.
道格-贝利的部分技能
Part of Doug Bailey's skill set
就是知道部门的重点是什么
is knowing where the department's focus is
因为资金是由重点组成的。
because funding follows focus.
我相信你已经读过了
And as I'm sure you've read,
联邦调查局认为国内恐怖主义
the FBI considers domestic terrorism
是对这个国家增长最快的威胁。
to be the fastest growing threat to this country.
快速增长的威胁是有钱的。
There's money in fast-growing threats.
连环杀手则没有。
There's none in serial killers.
他想关闭BAU。
He wants to shut down the BAU.
不是关闭。
Not shut down.
我看到的提案要求进行重组。
The proposal I saw calls for a reorganization.
该部门将被并入国内恐怖主义部门。
The unit would be folded under Domestic Terrorism.
他可以引入新的领导层
He can bring in new leadership
如果他能证明目前的领导层是浪费的。
if he can show that the current one is wasteful.
但我们不是。
But we're not.
从他的最后一次预算来看，你是。
You are as of his last budget.
关于一个运输集装箱的事情。
Something about a shipping container.
狗娘养的。
Son of a bitch.
他一直在陷害我们。
He's been setting us up this whole time.
我们会怎么样？
What happens with us?
重新分配。
Reassigned.
被替换。
Replaced.
退役。
Retired.
丽贝卡，谢谢你。
Rebecca, thank you.
我需要和单位说话，请。
I need to speak with the unit, please.
那么... ... 就这样了吗？
So is... is this it?
结束了吗？
Is it over?
不，还没有结束。
No, it's not over.
我们才刚刚开始。
We're just getting started.
是的，但我们有什么动作？
Yeah, but what moves do we have?
我是说，这家伙是副局长。
I mean, the guy's the Deputy Director.
我们用他自己的说法来反对他。
We use his own argument against him.
他想要国内恐怖主义。
He wants domestic terrorism.
我们有一个连环杀人网络。
We have a serial-killing network.
这就是国内恐怖主义。
That is domestic terrorism.
如果我们抓住他们，如果我们关闭这个网络，
If we catch them, if we shut down the network,
如果我们阻止西卡利斯...
if we stop Sicarius...
我们就能证明我们所做的是正确的
We justify what we do.
甚至贝利也不能碰我们。
Not even Bailey can touch us.
所以这是一场比赛。
So it's a race.
我们必须在UnSubs之前拿到那些杀戮工具。
We've got to get to those kill kits before the UnSubs.
是的，而且不允许有任何差错。
Yeah, and with no margin for error.
一旦贝利知道我们在做什么，
Once Bailey knows what we're up to,
他就会利用任何错误来对付我们。
he'll use any mistakes against us.
也许吧。
Maybe.
但我们有一个秘密武器。
But we have a secret weapon.
让我们开始工作吧。
Let's get to work.
# 哦！ #
♪ Oh! ♪
# 哦！ # # Oh!
? Oh! ?
♪ Oh! ♪